[
  {
    "Front": "ἰατρός",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: læge"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἰδέα",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: form, udseende"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἴδιος",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: egen"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἰδιώτης",
    "Back": " sb. 1 m.: privatperson"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἱερεύς",
    "Back": " sb. 3 m.: præst"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἱερόν",
    "Back": " sb. 2 n.: helligdom"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἱερός",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: hellig"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἵηµι",
    "Back": " vb. ureg.: sender"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἱκανός",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: tilstrækkelig"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἱκέτης",
    "Back": " sb. 1m.: flygtning (der søger hjælp)"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἱκνέοµαι",
    "Back": " vb. ureg.: (an)kommer"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἱµάτιον",
    "Back": " sb. 2 n.: overklædning, kappe"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἵνα",
    "Back": " konj. $: for at; hvor"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἱππεύς",
    "Back": " sb. 3 m.: rytter"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἵππος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: hest"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἴσος",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: lig(e stor)"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἵστηµι",
    "Back": " vb. ureg.: stiller"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἰσχυρός",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: stærk"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἰσχύς",
    "Back": " sb. 3 f.: styrke"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἴσως",
    "Back": " adv.: måske"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἰχθύς",
    "Back": " sb. 3 m.: fisk"
  }
]